ochef.com 2014-11-22

# Ochef.com Privacy Policy

Ochef.com Privacy Policy

Ochef.com is produced by the FNS, LLC, doing business under the name Food News Service. This policy covers all sites produced by FNS. This policy does not cover information collected on sites linked from FNS sites. 

FNS is committed to bringing you information that is tailored to your needs and, at the same time, to protecting your privacy. The following is a summary of the various ways we treat the information you provide us while using our site. 

FNS only collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent, and in almost all cases, you can access and use our sites without providing any personal information. For instance, when you register for our services, enter a sweepstakes or contest, or complete a survey, you may be asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name, or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested. 

FNS uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you submit a question to the chefs, we will use your e-mail address to let you know when the question has been answered. We may also use this information, with your consent, to send you regular e-mail newsletters, inform you about new features, products or services, or other changes to the services. 

FNS does not sell any of our users' personal information. We may, however, with your consent, share information with carefully selected companies that we think can offer you services and products of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your information shared, write to us using the Contact Us link at the bottom of most pages. If you do not wish to receive communications from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail. 

You may have read about "cookies," nuggets of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We do not use cookies currently. If we implement the use of cookies later, it will be for such purposes as controlling the display of ads, tracking usage patterns on the site or to record registration and personalization information. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve certain ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide you with those services. Any third party which has access to our database for this purpose is bound by the terms set forth in this policy. 

Finally, while your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our visitors as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing customer trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; notice of changes will appear on this page, so check back occasionally. Any such changes will be prospective, never retroactive. 

If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please write to us using the Contact Us link at the bottom of most pages. We welcome your feedback. You can also write us at the following address: 

Privacy Policy Coordinator   
FNS, LLC   
107 Pleasant St., Suite 1   
Brunswick, ME 04011   
USA
